<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>Context Sensitive Help for Recipient lists</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table>sys_dmail_group</csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:direct_mail/locallang_csh_sysdmailg.xml</fileId>
        <labelContext type="array">
            <label index=".description"></label>
            <label index=".details"></label>
            <label index="_.seeAlso"></label>
	    <label index="type.description"></label>
            <label index="type.details"></label>
	    <label index="title.description"></label>
            <label index="title.details"></label>
	    <label index="description.description"></label>
            <label index="description.details"></label>
	    <label index="pages.description"></label>
            <label index="pages.details"></label>
	    <label index="recursive.description"></label>
            <label index="recursive.details"></label>
	    <label index="whichtables.description"></label>
            <label index="whichtables.details"></label>
	    <label index="select_categories.description"></label>
            <label index="select_categories.details"></label>
	    <label index="list.description"></label>
            <label index="list.details"></label>
	    <label index="csv.description"></label>
            <label index="csv.details"></label>
	    <label index="static_list.description"></label>
            <label index="static_list.details"></label>
	    <label index="mail_groups.description"></label>
            <label index="mail_groups.details"></label>
        </labelContext>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
            <label index=".description">A list of recipients of direct mails</label>
            <label index=".details">Recipient lists are used by the Direct mail module to send newsletters to a group of recipients.
	    
There are five types of Recipient lists:

1.From pages: a list dynamically built from records found on pages of the website; you select the pages with the Starting Point field; you may include records from subtrees using the Include page subtree checkbox; you must specify the type(s) of records to include: Address, Website User, Website User Group and/or From custom-defined Table; if Website User Group is checked and a Website User Group is found, all Website Users members of the group will be included in the list; you may also restrict the selection of records to those with specific categories assignments;

2.Plain list: a list of email addresses separated by space, comma  or line break; if you change the List format, you may rather enter, one per line, a name and address, separated by a comma; sending Direct mail to such list will send only plain text email messages; moreover, only non-categorized content will be sent;

3.Static list: a list of individually selected records; the type of record may be Address, Website User, or Website User Group; if a  Website User Group is selected, all Website Users members of the group will be included in the list;

4.Special query: a list dynamically built using a SQL query; after creating the list, you may specify the query against one of the tables: Address, Website User or Custom-defined Table; to do so, you must select the Recipient list function of the Direct Mail module and click on the title of the list;

5.From other recipient lists: a list dynamically built from other recipient lists individually selected from the Recipient list table.</label>
            <label index="_.seeAlso">sys_dmail, sys_dmail_category</label>
	    <label index="type.description">Select the type of recipient list.</label>
            <label index="type.details">There are five types of Recipient lists:

1.From pages: a list dynamically built from records found on pages of the website; you select the pages with the Starting Point field; you may include records from subtrees using the Include page subtree checkbox; you must specify the type(s) of records to include: Address, Website User, Website User Group and/or From custom-defined Table; if Website User Group is checked and a Website User Group is found, all Website Users members of the group will be included in the list; you may also restrict the selection of records to those with specific categories assignments;

2.Plain list: a list of email addresses separated by space, comma  or line break; if you change the List format, you may rather enter, one per line, a name and address, separated by a comma; sending Direct mail to such list will send only plain text email messages; moreover, only non-categorized content will be sent;

3.Static list: a list of individually selected records; the type of record may be Address, Website User, or Website User Group; if a  Website User Group is selected, all Website Users members of the group will be included in the list;

4.Special query: a list dynamically built using a SQL query; after creating the list, you may specify the query against one of the tables: Address, Website User or Custom-defined Table; to do so, you must select the Recipient list function of the Direct Mail module and click on the title of the list;

5.From other recipient lists: a list dynamically built from other recipient lists individually selected from the Recipient list table.</label>
	    <label index="title.description">Enter the title of the recipient list.</label>
            <label index="title.details">This is the name that will be used to refer to this list.</label>
	    <label index="description.description">Enter a textual description of the recipient list.</label>
            <label index="description.details">This is a description that may document the purpose, use and/or content of the recipient list.</label>
	    <label index="pages.description">Select entry points in the page tree of the site.</label>
            <label index="pages.details">You may select here one or more pages in the page tree of the site. The pages will be searched for records that match the conditions specified by the other fields on the form.</label>
	    <label index="recursive.description">Check the box if you want to include all pages of the subtrees in the search.</label>
            <label index="recursive.details">If the box is checked, all pages included in the page subtrees of the entry points will also be searched for records that match the conditions specified by the other fields on the form.</label>
	    <label index="whichtables.description">Check the types of records you want to be included in the recipient list.</label>
            <label index="whichtables.details">Check the record types to be selected on the pages specified for constructing the recipient list.</label>
	    <label index="select_categories.description">Check the categories to which selected recipients must be subscribed.</label>
            <label index="select_categories.details">If you check one or more categories, only recipients subscribed to at least one of these categories will be included.</label>
	    <label index="list.description">Enter the list of email addresses of the recipient list.</label>
            <label index="list.details">Enter a list of email addresses separated by space, comma, or line break. If you change the list format, you may rather enter one entry per line as follows: name and address, separated by a comma.</label>
	    <label index="csv.description">Select the format you wish to use for entering the list od recipients.</label>
            <label index="csv.details">The emails entered in the list of recipients should be entered using the format you select here.</label>
	    <label index="static_list.description">Select the recipients you wish to include in the recipient list.</label>
            <label index="static_list.details">You may select recipients of the following types: Address, Website User or Website User Group. If you include a Website User Group, all Website Users members of the group will be included in the list.</label>
	    <label index="mail_groups.description">Select the recipient lists that you want to include in the current one.</label>
            <label index="mail_groups.details">You may select any recipient list other than the current one. All recipients included in the selected lists will the included in the current one.</label>
        </languageKey>
        <languageKey index="fr" type="array">
            <label index=".description">Liste de distribution d'envoi ciblé</label>
            <label index=".details">Les listes de distribution sont utilisées par le module d'Envoi ciblé pour envoyer des bulletins à des groupes de destinataines ou d'abonnés.

Il existe cinq types de listes de distribution:

1.Depuis certaines pages: une liste construite de manière dynamique à partir des enregistrements trouvés sur certaines pages du site; vous sélectionnez les pages au moyen du champ Point d'entrée; vous pouvez inclure les enregistrements de l'arborescence en cochant la case Inclure l'arborescence; vous devez spécifier les tables dont les enregistrements seront sélectionnés: Adresse, Utilisateur du site, Groupe d'utilisateurs du site et/ou Table définie sur mesure; si la case Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est cochée et si un Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est trouvé, tous les utilisateurs du site membres de ce groupe seront inclus dans la liste; vous pouvez également restreindre la sélection des enregistrements à ceux qui sont abonnés à certaines rubriques;

2.Liste simple: une liste d'adresses de courrier électronique séparées par des espaces, virgules ou sauts à la ligne; si vous changez le format de la liste, vous pouvez plutôt entrer, à raison d'une adresse par ligne, un nom et une adresse, séparés par une virgule; un envoi ciblé vers une telle liste n'enverra que des messages en format texte simple; de plus, seuls les éléments de contenu ne portant aucune rubrique seront inclus dans l'envoi;

3.Liste statique: une liste d'enregistrements sélectionnés individuellement des tables Adresse, Utilisateur de site et/ou Groupe d'utilisateurs du site; si un Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est sélectionné, tous les utilisateurs du site membres de ce groupe seront inclus dans la liste;

4.Requête spéciale: une liste construite de manière dynamique au moyen d'une requête SQL; après avoir d'abord créé la liste de distribution, vous pouvez spécifier la requête contre l'une des tables suivantes: Adresse, Utilisateur de site ou Table définie sur mesure; pour ce faire, vous devez sélectionner la fonction Listes de distribution du module d'Envoi ciblé et cliquer sur le titre de la liste;

5.Depuis d'autres listes de distribution: une liste construite de manière dynamique à partir d'autres listes de distribution sélectionnées individuellement de la table Liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="_.seeAlso">sys_dmail, sys_dmail_category</label>
	    <label index="type.description">Sélectionnez le type de liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="type.details">Il existe cinq types de listes de distribution:

1.Depuis certaines pages: une liste construite de manière dynamique à partir des enregistrements trouvés sur certaines pages du site; vous sélectionnez les pages au moyen du champ Point d'entrée; vous pouvez inclure les enregistrements de l'arborescence en cochant la case Inclure l'arborescence; vous devez spécifier les tables dont les enregistrements seront sélectionnés: Adresse, Utilisateur du site, Groupe d'utilisateurs du site et/ou Table définie sur mesure; si la case Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est cochée et si un Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est trouvé, tous les utilisateurs du site membres de ce groupe seront inclus dans la liste; vous pouvez également restreindre la sélection des enregistrements à ceux qui sont abonnés à certaines rubriques;

2.Liste simple: une liste d'adresses de courrier électronique séparées par des espaces, virgules ou sauts à la ligne; si vous changez le format de la liste, vous pouvez plutôt entrer, à raison d'un destinataire par ligne, le nom et l'adresse, séparés par une virgule; un envoi ciblé vers une telle liste n'enverra que des messages en format texte simple; de plus, seuls les éléments de contenu ne portant aucune rubrique seront inclus dans l'envoi;

3.Liste statique: une liste d'enregistrements sélectionnés individuellement;  des tables Adresse, Utilisateur de site et/ou Groupe d'utilisateurs du site; si un Groupe d'utilisateurs du site est sélectionné, tous les utilisateurs du site membres de ce groupe seront inclus dans la liste;

4.Requête spéciale: une liste construite de manière dynamique au moyen d'une requête SQL; après avoir d'abord créé la liste de distribution, vous pouvez spécifier la requête contre l'une des tables suivantes: Adresse, Utilisateur de site ou Table définie sur mesure; pour ce faire, vous devez sélectionner la fonction Listes de distribution du module d'Envoi ciblé et cliquer sur le titre de la liste;

5.Depuis d'autres listes de distribution: une liste construite de manière dynamique à partir d'autres listes de distribution sélectionnées individuellement de la table Liste de distribution.</label>
	    <label index="title.description">Entrez le titre de la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="title.details">Il s'agit du nom qui sera utilisé pour référer à cette liste.</label>
	    <label index="description.description">Entrez une description textuelle de la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="description.details">Il s'agit d'une description qui documente la raison d'être, l'utilisation et/ou le contenu de cette liste de distribution.</label>
	    <label index="pages.description">Sélectionnez des points d'entrée dans l'arborescence du site.</label>
            <label index="pages.details">Vous pouvez sélectionner une ou plusieurs pages dans l'arborescence du site. La liste de distribution sera construite en recherchant dans ces pages les enregistrements qui satisfont les critères spécifiés par les autres champs du formulaire.</label>
	    <label index="recursive.description">Cochez la case si vous désirez inclure les arborescences dans la construction de la liste.</label>
            <label index="recursive.details">Si la case est cochée, la liste de distribution sera construite en recherchant non seulement dans les pages servant de points d'entrée mais aussi dans toute l'arborescence de leurs sous-pages les enregistrements qui satisfont les critères spécifiés par les autres champs du formulaire.</label>
	    <label index="whichtables.description">Cochez les types d'enregistrements à inclure dans la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="whichtables.details">Cochez un ou plusieurs types d'enregistrements que vous voulez voir inclus la liste de distribution.</label>
	    <label index="select_categories.description">Cochez les rubriques auxquelles doivent être abonnés les destinataires de la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="select_categories.details">Si vous cochez une ou plusieurs rubriques, seuls les destinataires abonnés à l'une de ces rubriques seront inclus dans la liste.</label>
	    <label index="list.description">Entrez la liste des adresses de courrier électronique des destinataires de la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="list.details">Entrez une liste d'adresses de courrier électronique séparées par des espaces, des virgules ou des sauts à la ligne. Selon le choix de format de la liste, vous pouvez aussi entrer, à raison d'un destinataire par ligne, le nom et l'adresse, séparés par une virgule.</label>
	    <label index="csv.description">Choisissez le format dans lequel vous voulez entrer la liste des destinataires.</label>
            <label index="csv.details">Les adresses des destinataires doivent être entrées dans le format spécifié ici.</label>
	    <label index="static_list.description">Choisissez les destinataires que vous désirez inclure dans la liste de distribution.</label>
            <label index="static_list.details">Vous pouvez inclure dans la liste des destinataires de type: Adresse, Utilisateur de site ou Groupe d'utilisateurs du site. Si vous sélectionnez un Groupe d'utilisateurs du site, tous les utilisateurs du site membres de ce groupe seront inclus dans la liste de distribution.</label>
	    <label index="mail_groups.description">Choisissez les listes de distribution que vous désirez inclure dans celle-ci.</label>
            <label index="mail_groups.details">Vous pouvez inclure toute liste de distribution autre que la liste courante. Tous les destinataires inclus dans les listes choisis seront inclus dans la liste courante.</label>
        </languageKey>
    </data>
    <orig_hash type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
            <label index=".description" type="integer">247018705</label>
            <label index=".details" type="integer">65962995</label>
            <label index="_.seeAlso" type="integer">29877147</label>
        </languageKey>
        <languageKey index="fr" type="array">
            <label index=".description" type="integer">247018705</label>
            <label index=".details" type="integer">65962995</label>
            <label index="_.seeAlso" type="integer">29877147</label>
        </languageKey>
    </orig_hash>
    <orig_text type="array">
        <languageKey index="default" type="array">
        </languageKey>
        <languageKey index="fr" type="array">
        </languageKey>
    </orig_text>
</T3locallang>